# **Naresh Poudel**

Email: citenaresh@gmail.com

Phone: 0410238448 Perth, WA Australia

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/naresh-raj-poudel-94bb89203/

GitHub: https://github.com/citenaresh

## Summary

As a free-lance programmer I have experience in web app developing in both front end and back end development in those years I studied and implemented technologies such as HTML JavaScript, CSS, node, express, SQL, and Python. In the mean time I have been working as a chef for various restaurant which provides me extensive experience of high pressure fast paced environment as well as accurate and correct measurement, procedure and creation of many culinary items and how to provide the best customer service.

**Excellent Interpersonal Communication** 

Fluency in reading, writing and speaking English, Nepali and Hindi

## **Career History**

## Chef at The Coffee Club

Apr 2019 - Present (1 year and 10 months)

Preparing food for the customer. Plating the food to serve Ordering food items from the supplier

Stock taking

Using Database software

## Accountant and IT Manager Monsis Café, Claremont

June 2013-Dec 2018

Managing overall IT In the café and managing all the accounting works

## Freelance Web Desiner

From 2005

I design the website for Monsis café, The Sunrise Restaurant-Moonee ponds Melbourne, Salt and

Ginger (saltnginger.com)

Created a match making software for bishnurajkharel.com

# Education

# Coding Bootcamp from University of western Australia

Nov 2020-May 2021

# Certificate IV in Laboratory Techniques from TAFE WA

Graduated 2019

## Advance Diploma in Hospitality Management from Australian national Institute of

Business and Technology

Graduated 2011

## Diploma in Software Engineering from College of Software Engineering,

Narayangarh Nepal Graduated 2004

## **Projects**

## **Weather Dashboard**

A web app to find weather condition of a certain city with five days forecast for that place

## **Note Taker**

A web application which is used for writing and saving notes

# Reci-bits(Project 1 of Bootcamp)

Reci-bits is a web app designed to search recipe and nutrition information using APIs